Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938 P0006
Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938
- Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938., Items: 2,280 images. Approximately 3.57 Linear Feet. Nine document boxes and five drawers in map case.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Hazel-Nash House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0298)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2757.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Heartsease (Governor Thomas Burke House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0299)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2753.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Heartsease (Governor Thomas Burke House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0300)
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Houses (miscellaneous), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0301)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2484-2485, NC2756; Includes copy negatives.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Houses (miscellaneous), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0302)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2756.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Little Hawfield Plantation (Ruffin-DeRoulhac House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0303)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2769, NC2772-2773; Includes copy negatives.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Little Hawfield Plantation (Ruffin-DeRoulhac House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0304)
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Lochiel Mary Reid Anderson (Cameron) House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0305)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2765; Includes copy negative.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Orange County Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0306)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2754.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Orange County Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0307)
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Saint Matthews Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0308)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2768.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: Saint Matthews Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0309)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2768.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: San Souci Latta House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0310)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2775-2776.
  - Orange County: Hillsborough: San Souci Latta House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0311)
  - Pasquotank County: Elizabeth City: Blackbeard House (Brick House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0312)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2792-2793, NC2495.
  - Pasquotank County: Elizabeth City: Blackbeard House (Brick House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0313)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2793.
  - Pasquotank County: Nixonton: Lane House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0314)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2797.
  - Pasquotank County: Nixonton: Houses (miscellaneous), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0315)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2799-NC2800.
  - Pasquotank County: Nixonton: Pendleton, Morris, Barclift House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0316)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2798, NC2801.
  - Pasquotank County: Nixonton: Hinton-Morgan House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0317)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2802-2807.
  - Pasquotank County: South Mills: Hinton-Morgan House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0318)
  - Pender County: Hampstead: Sloop Point, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0319)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2809-2813.
  - Pender County: Hampstead: Sloop Point, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0320)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2811, NC2813.
  - Perquimans County: Harvey's Neck: Ashland, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0321)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2819.
  - Perquimans County: Harvey's Neck: Ashland, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0322)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2819.
  - Perquimans County: Harvey's Neck: Newbold-White House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0323)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2817-2818; Includes (deteriorated) negative.
  - Perquimans County: Harvey's Neck: Newbold-White House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0324)
  - Perquimans County: Hertford: Skinner's Farm, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0325)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2822.
  - Perquimans County: Hertford: Skinner's Farm, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0326)
  - Perquimans County: Hertford: Land's End (Leigh House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0327)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2820-2821.
  - Perquimans County: Hertford: Land's End (Leigh House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0328)
  - Perquimans County: Winfall: Belvidere, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0329)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2815-2816.
  - Perquimans County: Winfall: Belvidere, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 4, Oimage P0006/0330)
  - Polk County: Green River Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 24 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0331)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2823-2829, NC2831-2839.
  - Polk County: Columbus: Polk County Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0332)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2850; Includes copy negative.
  - Polk County: Mills Spring: Nite Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0333)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2849.
  - Polk County: Saluda: Morris Log Cabin, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0334)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2841-2845; Includes copy negatives.
  - Polk County: Saluda: Thames Place (Thompson House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0335)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2853, NC2855, NC2857.
  - Polk County: Tyron: Mills House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0336)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2847-2848.
  - Polk County: Tyron: Seven Heaths, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0337)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2851-2852.
  - Randolph County: Enos Blair Log House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0338)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2862-2864.
  - Randolph County: New Market Township: Frazier House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0339)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2858-2861.
  - Rockingham County: Wentworth: Log Barn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0340)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2953-2954.
  - Rockingham County: Wentworth: Wright Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 6, Bwpprint P0006/0341)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2948-2950; Includes original negative.
  - Rockingham County: Wentworth: Wright Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Bwpprint P0006/0436)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2950
  - Rowan County: Foard House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0342)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2890.
  - Rowan County: Hobson's Castle, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0343)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2894.
  - Rowan County: Irwin House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0344)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2895.
  - Rowan County: Oakland (Joseph Kerr House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0345)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2896.
  - Rowan County: Owen-Harrison House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0346)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2891-2892.
  - Rowan County: Third Creek Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0347)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2932.
  - Rowan County: Thyatria Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0348)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2931; Includes copy negative.
  - Rowan County: Bear Poplar: Wood Grove/Cowan House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 11 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0349)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2933-2936; Includes copy negatives.
  - Rowan County: Bear Poplar: Wood Grove/Cowan House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0350)
  - Rowan County: China Grove: Grace Lower Stone Lutheran Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/035)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2914-2915, NC2918-NC2919.
  - Rowan County: China Grove: Grace Lower Stone Lutheran Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0352)
  - Rowan County: China Grove: John Stigerwalt House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0353)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2923, NC2926, NC29930; Includes copy negative.
  - Rowan County: China Grove: John Stigerwalt House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0354)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Archibald Henderson Law Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0355)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2983.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Boyden House Mantel, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0356)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2865.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Boyden House Mantel, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0357)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Cicero Barker House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0358)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2866.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Hall House (McNeely Strachan), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0359)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2899-2900; Includes copy negatives.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Hall House (McNeely Strachan), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0360)
    One image is framed.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: John Knox Cabin, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0361)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2897.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Lomabardy (Steelworth) House Mantels, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0362)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2912-2913; Includes copy negatives.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Lombardy (Steelworth) House Mantels, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0363)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Michael Braun House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0364)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2868-2870.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Michael Braun House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0365)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Michael Braun Stone House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0366)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2867, NC2871, NC2873-2874.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Presbyterian Manse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0367)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2908-2911.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Presbyterian Manse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0368)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Rowan County Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0369)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2888-2889.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: Rowan County Courthouse, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0370)
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: State Bank of North Carolina, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0371)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2919-2920, NC2922; Includes copy negatives.
  - Rowan County: Salisbury: State Bank of North Carolina, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0372)
  - Rowan County: Sowers Ferry: Alexander Long House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0373)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2903-2905.
  - Rowan County: Sowers Ferry: Alexander Long House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0374)
  - Rowan County: Spencer: Maxwell Chambers House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 17 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0375)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2875, NC2876, NC2878, NC2880-2881, NC2883-2886, NC2878.
  - Rowan County: Spencer: Maxwell Chambers House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0376)
  - Rowan County: Trading Ford Road: Linn House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0377)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2898.
  - Rutherford County: McClure House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0378)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2943-2944.
  - Rutherford County: Miller House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0379)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2946.
  - Rutherford County: Lake Lure, Pine Gables, Logan House, Red Coach Inn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 print (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0380)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2633 (or 2637).
  - Rutherford County: Westmister: Andrews Log House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0381)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2937-NC2938.
  - Rutherford County: Westmister: Jim Andrews House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0382)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2939-2940.
  - Rutherford County: Westmister: Little Brittain Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0383)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2941-2942.
  - Tyrell County: Lake Phelps: Josiah Collins Plantation (Somerset), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0384)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2955-2957.
  - Tyrell County: Lake Phelps: Josiah Collins Plantation (Somerset), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0385)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2957.
  - Vance County: Pleasant Hill (Riven Oaks), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0386)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2977-2978, NC2980.
  - Vance County: Henderson: Samuel Henderson House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0387)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2972-2973.
  - Vance County: Henderson: Samuel Henderson House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0388)
  - Vance County: Henderson: Harris Mill, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0389)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2968; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Vance County: Henderson: Richard Henderson House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0390)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2974.
  - Vance County: Townsville: Boley Hunt House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0391)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2969-2971.
  - Vance County: Townsville: Boley Hunt House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0392)
  - Vance County: Townsville: Hiberia, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0393)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2975-NC2976; Includes copy negatives.
  - Vance County: Williamsboro: Blooming Hope, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0394)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2966-NC2967; Includes copy negatives.
  - Vance County: Williamsboro: Burnside, Hunt Hamilton House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 12 images (Printbox 7, Bwpprint P0006/0395)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2960, NC2962-2964; Includes copy negatives.
  - Vance County: Williamsboro: Burnside, Hunt Hamilton House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0396)
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Rectory, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0397)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3015-3012; Includes copy negatives.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0398)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3015-3016.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0399)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC23015.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: John Haywood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0400)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2982-2984; Includes copy negative.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: John Haywood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0401)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2981 and NC2984.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Midway Plantation (Mary Hillard Hinton House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0402)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2987.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: North Carolina State Capitol, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 17 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0403)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3019-3028, NC3069; Includes original negative.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: North Carolina State Capitol, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0404)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC3028.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Page Mill on Crabtree Creek, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0405)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3007; Includes copy negative.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Richard Haywood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0406)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2986; Includes copy negative.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Richard Haywood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0407)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2986.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Unidentified House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0408)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3017.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Wakefield, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0409)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2989, NC 2991-2993; Includes copy negative.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Wakefield (Joel Lane House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0410)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2992.
  - Wake County: Raleigh: Yates Mill, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0411)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3009-3011.
  - Warren County: Nathaniel Macon Homestead and Corncrib, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0412)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3051-3054; Includes copy negative.
  - Warren County: Inez: Mont Petross (Solomon Williams House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 11 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0413)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3094-3098; Includes copy negatives.
  - Warren County: Inez: Mont Petross (Solomon Williams House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0414)
  - Warren County: Inez: Saxham Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0415)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3104-3107; Includes copy negatives.